class TrophiesQuestions {
  static List<Map<String, dynamic>> trophyQuestions = [
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the Premier League?',
      'options': ['13', '15', '17', '20'],
      'answer': '13',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the Premier League 13 times as of 2023.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Which year did Manchester United win their first Premier League title?',
      'options': ['1993', '1994', '1995', '1996'],
      'answer': '1993',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United won their first Premier League title in the 1992-1993 season.'
    },
    {
      'question': 'How many times has Manchester United won the FA Cup?',
      'options': ['12', '14', '16', '18'],
      'answer': '12',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the FA Cup 12 times as of 2023.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who was the manager of Manchester United when they won their first FA Cup?',
      'options': [
        'Sir Matt Busby',
        'Sir Alex Ferguson',
        'Ron Atkinson',
        'Tommy Docherty'
      ],
      'answer': 'Sir Matt Busby',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Sir Matt Busby was the manager when Manchester United won their first FA Cup in 1948.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'In which year did Manchester United win their first League Cup?',
      'options': ['1992', '1994', '1996', '1998'],
      'answer': '1992',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United won their first League Cup in the 1991-1992 season.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1968 European Cup final to win their first European title?',
      'options': ['Benfica', 'Real Madrid', 'Inter Milan', 'AC Milan'],
      'answer': 'Benfica',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Benfica 4-1 in the 1968 European Cup final to win their first European title.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the UEFA Champions League?',
      'options': ['3', '4', '5', '6'],
      'answer': '3',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the UEFA Champions League 3 times (1968, 1999, 2008).'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who was the manager of Manchester United when they won their first UEFA Champions League title in 1968?',
      'options': [
        'Sir Matt Busby',
        'Sir Alex Ferguson',
        'Ron Atkinson',
        'Tommy Docherty'
      ],
      'answer': 'Sir Matt Busby',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Sir Matt Busby was the manager when Manchester United won their first UEFA Champions League title in 1968.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the FIFA Club World Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the FIFA Club World Cup once, in 2008.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 2008 FIFA Club World Cup final?',
      'options': ['LDU Quito', 'Boca Juniors', 'Santos', 'Palmeiras'],
      'answer': 'LDU Quito',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated LDU Quito 1-0 in the 2008 FIFA Club World Cup final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the Intercontinental Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the Intercontinental Cup once, in 1999.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1999 Intercontinental Cup final?',
      'options': ['Palmeiras', 'River Plate', 'Boca Juniors', 'Santos'],
      'answer': 'Palmeiras',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Palmeiras 1-0 in the 1999 Intercontinental Cup final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the UEFA Europa League?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the UEFA Europa League once, in 2017.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who was the manager of Manchester United when they won the UEFA Europa League in 2017?',
      'options': [
        'Jose Mourinho',
        'Louis van Gaal',
        'David Moyes',
        'Ole Gunnar Solskjær'
      ],
      'answer': 'Jose Mourinho',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Jose Mourinho was the manager when Manchester United won the UEFA Europa League in 2017.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the UEFA Super Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the UEFA Super Cup once, in 1991.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1991 UEFA Super Cup final?',
      'options': ['Red Star Belgrade', 'AC Milan', 'Juventus', 'Barcelona'],
      'answer': 'Red Star Belgrade',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Red Star Belgrade 1-0 in the 1991 UEFA Super Cup final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the Community Shield?',
      'options': ['21', '23', '25', '27'],
      'answer': '21',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the Community Shield 21 times as of 2023.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1999 Community Shield match?',
      'options': ['Arsenal', 'Liverpool', 'Chelsea', 'Tottenham Hotspur'],
      'answer': 'Arsenal',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Arsenal 2-1 in the 1999 Community Shield match.'
    },
    {
      'question': 'How many times has Manchester United won the League Cup?',
      'options': ['5', '6', '7', '8'],
      'answer': '5',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the League Cup 5 times as of 2023.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who was the manager of Manchester United when they won their first League Cup title in 1992?',
      'options': [
        'Alex Ferguson',
        'Ron Atkinson',
        'Tommy Docherty',
        'Matt Busby'
      ],
      'answer': 'Alex Ferguson',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Sir Alex Ferguson was the manager when Manchester United won their first League Cup title in 1992.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the FA Charity/Community Shield?',
      'options': ['21', '23', '25', '27'],
      'answer': '21',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the FA Charity/Community Shield 21 times as of 2023.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 2003 FA Community Shield match?',
      'options': ['Arsenal', 'Liverpool', 'Chelsea', 'Tottenham Hotspur'],
      'answer': 'Arsenal',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Arsenal 4-3 on penalties after a 1-1 draw in the 2003 FA Community Shield match.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the European Cup Winners\' Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the European Cup Winners\' Cup once, in 1991.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1991 European Cup Winners\' Cup final?',
      'options': ['FC Barcelona', 'Juventus', 'AC Milan', 'Red Star Belgrade'],
      'answer': 'FC Barcelona',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated FC Barcelona 2-1 in the 1991 European Cup Winners\' Cup final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the FIFA World Cup for Clubs?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the FIFA World Cup for Clubs once, in 2008.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 2008 FIFA World Cup for Clubs final?',
      'options': ['LDU Quito', 'Boca Juniors', 'Santos', 'Palmeiras'],
      'answer': 'LDU Quito',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated LDU Quito 1-0 in the 2008 FIFA World Cup for Clubs final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the European/South American Cup (Intercontinental Cup)?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the European/South American Cup (Intercontinental Cup) once, in 1999.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1999 European/South American Cup (Intercontinental Cup) final?',
      'options': ['Palmeiras', 'River Plate', 'Boca Juniors', 'Santos'],
      'answer': 'Palmeiras',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Palmeiras 1-0 in the 1999 European/South American Cup (Intercontinental Cup) final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the UEFA Cup/Europa League?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the UEFA Cup/Europa League once, in 2017.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who was the manager of Manchester United when they won the UEFA Cup/Europa League in 2017?',
      'options': [
        'Jose Mourinho',
        'Louis van Gaal',
        'David Moyes',
        'Ole Gunnar Solskjær'
      ],
      'answer': 'Jose Mourinho',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Jose Mourinho was the manager when Manchester United won the UEFA Cup/Europa League in 2017.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the UEFA Super Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the UEFA Super Cup once, in 1991.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1991 UEFA Super Cup final?',
      'options': ['Red Star Belgrade', 'AC Milan', 'Juventus', 'Barcelona'],
      'answer': 'Red Star Belgrade',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Red Star Belgrade 1-0 in the 1991 UEFA Super Cup final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the English League Cup?',
      'options': ['5', '6', '7', '8'],
      'answer': '5',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the English League Cup 5 times as of 2023.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who was the manager of Manchester United when they won their first English League Cup title in 1992?',
      'options': [
        'Alex Ferguson',
        'Ron Atkinson',
        'Tommy Docherty',
        'Matt Busby'
      ],
      'answer': 'Alex Ferguson',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Sir Alex Ferguson was the manager when Manchester United won their first English League Cup title in 1992.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the FA Community Shield?',
      'options': ['21', '23', '25', '27'],
      'answer': '21',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the FA Community Shield 21 times as of 2023.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1999 FA Community Shield match?',
      'options': ['Arsenal', 'Liverpool', 'Chelsea', 'Tottenham Hotspur'],
      'answer': 'Arsenal',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Arsenal 2-1 in the 1999 FA Community Shield match.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup once, in 1991.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1991 UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup final?',
      'options': ['FC Barcelona', 'Juventus', 'AC Milan', 'Red Star Belgrade'],
      'answer': 'FC Barcelona',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated FC Barcelona 2-1 in the 1991 UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the FIFA Club World Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the FIFA Club World Cup once, in 2008.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 2008 FIFA Club World Cup final?',
      'options': ['LDU Quito', 'Boca Juniors', 'Santos', 'Palmeiras'],
      'answer': 'LDU Quito',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated LDU Quito 1-0 in the 2008 FIFA Club World Cup final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the Intercontinental Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the Intercontinental Cup once, in 1999.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1999 Intercontinental Cup final?',
      'options': ['Palmeiras', 'River Plate', 'Boca Juniors', 'Santos'],
      'answer': 'Palmeiras',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Palmeiras 1-0 in the 1999 Intercontinental Cup final.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the UEFA Europa League?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the UEFA Europa League once, in 2017.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who was the manager of Manchester United when they won the UEFA Europa League in 2017?',
      'options': [
        'Jose Mourinho',
        'Louis van Gaal',
        'David Moyes',
        'Ole Gunnar Solskjær'
      ],
      'answer': 'Jose Mourinho',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Jose Mourinho was the manager when Manchester United won the UEFA Europa League in 2017.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the UEFA Super Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the UEFA Super Cup once, in 1991.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1991 UEFA Super Cup final?',
      'options': ['Red Star Belgrade', 'AC Milan', 'Juventus', 'Barcelona'],
      'answer': 'Red Star Belgrade',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Red Star Belgrade 1-0 in the 1991 UEFA Super Cup final.'
    },
    {
      'question': 'How many times has Manchester United won the League Cup?',
      'options': ['5', '6', '7', '8'],
      'answer': '5',
      'points': 10,
      'info': 'Manchester United has won the League Cup 5 times as of 2023.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who was the manager of Manchester United when they won their first League Cup title in 1992?',
      'options': [
        'Alex Ferguson',
        'Ron Atkinson',
        'Tommy Docherty',
        'Matt Busby'
      ],
      'answer': 'Alex Ferguson',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Sir Alex Ferguson was the manager when Manchester United won their first League Cup title in 1992.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the FA Charity/Community Shield?',
      'options': ['21', '23', '25', '27'],
      'answer': '21',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the FA Charity/Community Shield 21 times as of 2023.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 2003 FA Community Shield match?',
      'options': ['Arsenal', 'Liverpool', 'Chelsea', 'Tottenham Hotspur'],
      'answer': 'Arsenal',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated Arsenal 4-3 on penalties after a 1-1 draw in the 2003 FA Community Shield match.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'How many times has Manchester United won the European Cup Winners\' Cup?',
      'options': ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      'answer': '1',
      'points': 10,
      'info':
          'Manchester United has won the European Cup Winners\' Cup once, in 1991.'
    },
    {
      'question':
          'Who did Manchester United defeat in the 1991 European Cup Winners\' Cup final?',
      'options': ['FC Barcelona', 'Juventus', 'AC Milan', 'Red Star Belgrade'],
      'answer': 'FC Barcelona',
      'points': 15,
      'info':
          'Manchester United defeated FC Barcelona 2-1 in the 1991 European Cup Winners\' Cup final.'
    }
  ];

  List<String> questionsOnly =
      trophyQuestions.map((quiz) => quiz['question'] as String).toList();

  List<int> pointsOnly =
      trophyQuestions.map((quiz) => quiz['points'] as int).toList();

  List<List<String>> optionsOnly =
      trophyQuestions.map((quiz) => quiz['options'] as List<String>).toList();
  List<String> infoOnly =
      trophyQuestions.map((quiz) => quiz['info'] as String).toList();

  List<int> correctAnswerIndexes = trophyQuestions.map((quiz) {
    List<String> options = quiz['options'];
    String answer = quiz['answer'];
    return options.indexOf(answer);
  }).toList();
}
